Some call it organized crime. Others call it family.
The Family is a crime, comedy, action film directed by Luc Besson.
After ratting out his Mafia cohorts, Giovanni Manzoni and his family enter the
Witness Protection Program and relocate to a sleepy town in France.
Despite the best efforts of their handler to keep them in line, Giovanni (now called Fred
Blake), his wife and children can't help but resort to doing things the "family" way.
However, their dependence on such old habits places
everyone in danger from vengeful mobsters.
Fred Blake / Giovanni Manzoni, played by Robert De Niro.
Maggie Blake, played by Michelle Pfeiffer.
FBI Agent Robert Stansfield, played by Tommy Lee Jones.
Belle Blake, played by Dianna Agron.
Warren Blake, played by John D'Leo.
Rocco, played by Jon Freda.
The Family (released as Malavita and Cosa Nostra in some countries) is a 2013 black comedy crime film co-written and
directed by Luc Besson, starring Robert De Niro, Michelle Pfeiffer, Tommy Lee Jones, Dianna Agron and John D'Leo.
A co-production between France and the United States, the film follows a Mafia
family in the witness protection program who want to change their lives.
It is based on the 2004 novel Malavita (Badfellas in the 2010
English translation) by French author Tonino Benacquista.
The film explores themes of high school, france, based on
novel or book, sadistic, witness protection.
The tone is lighthearted.